

Matt Chen

+886 (0916-272-800)



dloygtw.il@gmail.com

3F., No.1, Linjiang St., Daan Dist., Taipei City 106, Taiwan (R.O.C.)

OBJECTIVE: WEB SERVICES ENGINEER in NVIDIA Job ID:1873818 Location: China, Shanghai

WORK EXPERIENCE

Programmer - 500NET Technology(Oct 2013-May2015)

- Developed and implemented customized E-commerce system
- Developed API of PHP to integrate Android and iOS system communication with Database
- Front end CSS3, HTML5 developed and Responsive Web Design
- Integrated credit card trading online system using PHP
- Database transition from MYSQL to MSSQL
- Projects: World-vision, First Bank customer complaint system, Wedding Consultant platform, Motor and motorcycle sensor management system

Q Memory Tuning Engineer- AMD Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (Sep 2011 - Jun 2013)

- Constantly updating and upgrading test stations to insure test results are accurate on Linux
- Graphic add in board and Graphic mobile platform design issue filter and debugging support (Hardware / Software)
- Used to validate and verify new design implementations, validation test coverage and quality specific on memory component
- Responsible for quality and timeliness of result for a portion of project/process
- Technical capability to ensure real time resolution of partner issues in locally
- Functional and Stress test to confirm the normal operation of the circuit board design
- Expertise on e-Lab project management system by implement Java, PHP and MySQL database

QA Engineer- CyberLink (July 2010 - Apr 2011)

- To record and describe bugs on tracking system.
- Test case writing to plan the entire testing scenario.
- Make check list for function test, UI test, boundary test.
- Experience of projects as Media Smart, Touch Smart, Youcam and PowerDVD Tunes Media Player

EDUCATION

- O National Taipei University Technology
 - Bachelors in Civil Engineering, June 2006

EXPERTISE

- PHP, JAVA, HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, CSS3, Responsive Web Design, SVN Tortoise, Apache Codeigniter MVC framework, Mantis Bug Tracker, Flash & ActionScript 3.0, Photoshop
- MSSQL, MYSQL, Oracle operation and implementation
- Linux , XAMPP, Appserv, Vmware, Tomcat
- Quality Assurance

PORTFOLIO

http://il.webhop.me/dloygtw

ABOUT ME

My first job about science and technology was in CyberLink Company which led a main media product in market. The position was QA Engineer. I had experienced software quality assurance and learned skills as Test Case Writing, Debugging, Function Test, Analysis and Tracking of Issues, discussing with RD to correct defects of product, how to manufacture perfect product to user's requirement. Experienced project as Media Smart, Touch Smart, YouCam, PowerDVD Tune Player.

After that, I had joined AMD Company to take responsibility in Memory Tuning Engineer in ATI Graphic Card / Chipsets deportment. I am in charge of tuning and verifying between Graphic chip and memory and customer service. Using Linux system to do automation test, I am also responsible for maintenance of E-lab Devices managementsystem using PHP, Java and MySQL, Oracle database. I had been the trainer of Database Language for colleagues.

The third work was in 500NET Technology Company afterwards. The position was Programmer. Developed PHP based E-commerce and integrated Credit Card trading online system. Front-End framework built of CSS3, HTML5 and Responsive Web Design. To develop communicated function between Database MYSQL and MSSQL. Upgraded new function legacy system or provide the solution for customer.

My personality is enthusiasm for job. Discrete, honest and conscientious; Keep calm when problems happen; I am also good at getting along with people and good emotion management. I believe I have been given the high commendation of this from former supervisors and colleagues; I am able to work under pressure and able to work as part of a team as well.

I have creation and also have accumulated QA and developed experiences of years. The most of important thing is I have passion in this industry. I want to keep understanding technique of Web Development for manufacturing product. Not only reach to requirement of high quality, but also make perfect product which will be my goal in the future.